{
    "id": "23199ebe4f5b4648bd4483d778464cbf",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was hungry ………………………… she hadn’t eaten anything in a long time.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason for something.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ae3aac14e037432f88baeac7c2da75f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… he is late, we will go without him.",
            "description": "Either could be used here with different meanings. If expresses a condition. As gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "177e4b9ba1b347d28693148a05ba2c10"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… he is fat, he runs slowly.",
            "description": "As gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "So"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "902aa2f9c84d4774b49cb3e8f90d621f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is neither intelligent …………………………….. hard working.",
            "description": "Note the pattern neither...nor.",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "668859676c9546688f5ecac91418fd76"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t talk to you now ………………………….. I am busy.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason for something.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6bbf1bf795bd4a45a24cfddf88e07e3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can watch TV …………………………….. you have finished your homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "after",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ebeab3f0234843a095663112fb00c316"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you are feeling cold, I will put the heating on.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96d3e818a2a845a2be1c4fee183f2cd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………… I had a headache, I enjoyed the party.",
            "description": "Even though is used to emphasize a contrast.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Even if",
                "Even though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "09fbd98719734f9c9e6df86882938970"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spoke so fast ………………………….. I could not follow him.",
            "description": "So shows the cause and that indicates the effect.",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "that",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5837aebf1a51420d8bf97e70f686e517"
        },
        {
            "question": "The faster you run, …………………………. you get tired.",
            "description": "The comparative is used in both clauses in this structure. The article 'the' cannot be omitted.",
            "answers": [
                "soon",
                "sooner",
                "the sooner"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cfbb9aa0ccd549aaba4bbd26ea04a20d"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. he is the fastest runner, he finished last.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "feaa722581ee42be9ff63fbc3f78069f"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house …………………………… I live.",
            "description": "Where means in which.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f4c29059af0e43a1b55ee25b00e444ec"
        }
    ]
}